MICHAEL LAW

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a driven and dedicated individual with a background in and passion for all types of technology. My interest in this industry is what drives me to learn and adapt to how quickly things change. I aspire to be a web developer, not only to make my own ideas come alive, but to be a part of the growth of the industry and the internet as we know it. I bring over a decade of office experience, excel working in groups and individually, and have a drive for personal and professional growth in programming.

CONTACT

6

(519) 766 - 5639



mikelaw86@hotmail.com



Fergus, Ontario



linkedin.com/in/mikelaw86



github.com/Law86

SKILLS

- Javascript, React, Ruby, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Normalize CSS
- Express, NodeJS, ReactJS, EJS
- Storybook, Cypress, Mocha, Chai, Jest
- PostgresSQL, SQL
- Windows, MacOS, Linux, iOS, Android

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Lighthouse Labs March - May 2022

Marketing

Fanshawe College 2006-2007

PROJECTS

Flashers

• A single page web app designed for urban boulderers to find local spots to climb, or flash. This app was a collaboration for our final project.

Stack: Node, Express, React, Axios, PostgreSQL, Google Maps API, Auth0.

LockD

 An easy to use and fun take on a password generator and storage app. This app was a collaboration for our midterm project.

Stack: EJS, SCSS, JavaScript, jQuery, NodeJS, BcryptJS, Express, PostgreSQL.

Scheduler

• Scheduler is a calendar used to book, edit and cancel interviews. It was created as part of the curriculum at Lighthouse Labs.

Stack: React, Axios, Classnames, Normalize CSS, Storybook, Jest, Cypress.

EXPERIENCE

Owner/Technician

Law Wire - Fergus, Ontario June 2022 - Present

- Independently operated company working with established audio visual companies for the installation of full smart home systems and equipment.
- Established upon completion of Web Development course to continue learning of the field, with flexibility of continuing to grow in web development.

Senior Technician

Station Earth - Fergus, Ontario December 2018 - March 2022

- Lead technician in charge of the planning, pre-wiring and installation of all types of technology. From full home ELAN systems and everything that falls under them, including cameras, speakers, touchpanels, tvs, wifi, etc.
- Largely in charge of small groups of technicians, between 1-3 employees depending on the job and requirements.